Contact

dev_gadhvi@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/devgadhvi10x (LinkedIn) devgadhvi.in (Personal) www.devgadhvi10x.com/ebook (Personal) www.instamojo.com/products (Personal)

Top Skills

Business Development Sales Marketing

Languages

Sindhi English Gujarati

Certifications

Cardone University - Sales Certification

Consultative Selling for Breakthrough Results

High Ticket Closer

Publications

80% Mindset 20% Skills

Dev Gadhvi - No.1 Passionpreneur Mentor

First Generation \$ Millionaire | Ask me - How to Quit Job & Become a Passionpreneur | Highly Paid Indian Influencer | CoFounder 1 Crore Coach | Twice Best Selling Author Pune

Summary

How a Truck Driver's Proud Son Quit his Job and Built a Coaching Business to become a First Generation \$ Millionaire within 29 Months?

I was born in a humble family where my parents struggled to get us the eduction in an English medium school

I struggled to speak proper English and hence I did not find jobs even in BPOs easily

After lots of effort finally I managed to get into decent jobs.

I worked in job for 16 years. Changed more than 8 companies to reach the monthly income of Rs. 3.5 lakhs

What I did not like is the fact that I was still following the orders and not following my PASSION!

I used to think that I was born to work in 9to5 for my whole life but then I found my Passion and Purpose.

I started to invest lots of money on my self development. It was Rs. 16 Lakhs in just 20 months.

What it did was, it helped me build my business around passion.

Within 2 years, I became highly paid Indian Influencer who charged Lakhs for my keynote speeches, mentorship fees and consulting. Became Best Selling Author, TEDx and JoshTalks Speaker, and an International Speaker.

I went from charging Rs. 1 lakh per client to Rs. 8 Lakhs within 20 months. Generated over Rs.10 Crore within 29 months!

Now, of course this was not a cake walk or smooth but it wasn't that complicated either. I understood that anyone can do what I am doing if they know what I learnt from my mentors like Dan Lok, Grant Cardone and others.

You must be wondering what exact steps did I follow and curious to know how you can learn them, right?

.

You can learn about my journey and my secrets in an easy step by step manner with my book 80% mindset 20% skills https://www.devgadhvi10x.com/ebook

"".

https://www.facebook.com/groups/351287591956566/

_

https://www.amazon.in/Sundays-Week-Life-Dev-Gadhvi-ebook/dp/B086LG84FW

Experience

1 Crore Coach Cofounder - 1 Crore Coach December 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months) Maharashtra, India

Dev Gadhvi Enterprise Founder of India's First Passionpreneur Mastermind April 2013 - Present (7 years 5 months) Pune Area, India

- > Helping people find their passion and build their business around it!
- > Helping people quit 9to5 life and build 6-Sundays-a-Week Life!
- > Helping passionpreneurs master the art of selling without selling Closing Big Deal with Ease!

- > Helping Passionpreneurs to build the Social Media Brand Content Creation, Content Distribution, Sales Funnels, Webinar Funnels, etc
- > Helping people to learn how to become best selling author and best impacting author
- > Helping people build financial confidence by creating multiple streams of income around passion
- > Training corporate teams to master sales and also inspire them to maximize their potential

Want to know more WhatsApp our team at +91 9819526252 or email us at dev@devgadhvi10x.com

JoshTalks

Keynote Speaker November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Gave a Keynote speech in Pune - "Are You a Rebel?"

TED Conferences

TEDx Speaker

October 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months)

Pune Area, India

Delivered a speech on a topic "Growing Beyond 9to5 and Building 6 Sundays A Week Life"

Amazon

#1 Best Selling Author - 80%Mindset 20%Skills February 2018 - Present (2 years 7 months) India

Dev has become the #1 Best Seller with his unconventional book that is transforming lives. He has received so many recognization for his book.

YouTube

India's Leading YouTuber
August 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month)

Pune Area, India

Dev Gadhvi has been interviewing successful people around the globe to share their knowledge and wisdom with others

Page 3 of 4

He has interviewed people like:

- > Patrick Bet David CEO of Valuetainment, Multimillionaire with multiple business in the U.S
- > Dan Lok King of High Ticket Sales, Multimillionaire with multiple business and best selling author of "FU Money" based out of Canada
- > Evan Carmichael Multimillionaire and leading YouTuber with more than a million subscribers, best selling author of "Your One Word"
- > Tony J Hughes Leading Sales Expert and Best Selling Author of "Joshua Principle" based out of Australia

and many others!

Dev has been inspiring thousands of people with his Carenation videos helping street vendors

Education

Dan Lok™ University
High Ticket Sales Expert, Selling Skills · (2017 - 2018)

Grant Cardone University
Sales Mastery, Selling Skills · (2016 - 2017)